

Azubuike Joseph Nwibo

Date of birth: 25 Apr 1995

Nationality: Nigerian (Nigeria)

Gender: Male

CONTACT

 Damagaza, behind Living Faith Church Lokogoma Abuja, Nigeria.

> Opposite Damagaza Primary health Center. 900104 AMAC, Nigeria

nwiboazubuike@gmail.com



(+234) 07086334804



(+234) 07053541229

Twitter: https://twitter.com/
nwibo_azubuike?
t=jUKQAQe8eemqO4YxFFgU8
w&s=09

Whatsapp Messenger: http://wa.me/qr/IMDJ2TA55T5HE1

ABOUT ME

I'm a type that loves education so much, I actually studied engineering due to my love for mathematics, chemistry and physics back then in secondary school, I'm a graduate of civil engineering technology, though later felled in love with web development and programming in general

Moving higher in research in civil/structural engineering and programming is my dreams.

WORK EXPERIENCE

AUG 2013 - NOV 2018 - Abakaliki, Nigeria

Teaching staff

Golden gate secondary school, ndiapkarata

Taught physics, chemistry and mathematics for senior secondary session

NOV 2021 - CURRENT - Ikot ekpene, Nigeria

Graduate Assistant

Akwaibom state polytechnic, ikot osurua.

Assisting the lab technologist to carry out experiments and to maintain safe and quiet atmosphere during practical's, also helping the lecturers to lecture the students on structural designs like CEC206, CEC306, CEC205, CEC106, CEC101, CEC405 etc.

NOV 2016 - FEB 2017 - Abakaliki, Nigeria

Lab technician

Ebonyi state ministry of works

Conducting practical's on soil mechanics laboratory and also concrete laboratory too

FEB 2020 - OCT 2020 - Abakaliki, Nigeria

Project supervisor

Ebonyi State pilling team

Supervision of pile foundation being casted at the terminal, Ebonyi State international cargo Airport

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

NOV 2015 - AUG 2017 - Afikpo North, Unwana, Afikpo, Nigeria

ND(Distinction)

Akanuibiam federal polytechnic unwana

Polyunwana.net

NOV 2018 - MAR 2021 - Afikpo North, Unwana, Afikpo, Nigeria

HND(Distinction)

Akanuibiam federal polytechnic, unwana

Polyunwana.net

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Igbo language

OTHER LANGUAGE(S):

English

Listening C1	Reading C1	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	Writing B2
		B2	C1	

DIGITAL SKILLS

Google Drive

Microsoft office

Microsoft Excel / Microsoft Word / Microsoft project

CAD skills

ArchiCAD / CSC Orion / AutoCAD

Social media

Instagram / Facebook / WhatsApp / Twitter / Skype **program**

/ HTML5/CSS, JavaScript /Tailwind CSS / MATLAB / React jS / Node jS / Express / MongoDB /

CONFERENCES AND SEMINARS

6 DEC 2021 – 10 DEC 2021 > – International conference center, Abuja.

Expansion of the Energy Mix for National Growth

PROJECTS

OCT 2020 - APR 2021

Structural design of one-story residential buildingwith 1.2 meters sit-out

Analytical design of the structure was carried out in all the elements (slab, beams, Columns, footings and staircase) including providing cross-sectional dimension, quantity and arrangement of reinforcement and other necessary checks against shear, cracking and deflection criterion when necessary

JAN 2017 - JUL 2017

Effect of saw dust and fiber inclusion in the production of blocks

Knowing the effects of saw dust and fiber in the strength of sand Crete blocks as compared to the normal sand Crete blocks

COMMUNICATION AND INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Oral and written

Love communication more especially during tutoring or lecturing and when writing thesis or exams

CREATIVE WORKS

APR 2019 - CURRENT

Architectural and structural drawings

Drawings on Architectural buildings and carrying out the corresponding structural drawings on AutoCAD

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Studying and football

Love studying structural design, solving mathematics and watching of football matches

coding

Loves bringing my ideas to reality, I can code 8hoursand more a day

ORGANISATIONAL SKILLS

Leadership

Leading as a course representative in Matrix and energy methods in structures during my undergraduate education.

HONOURS AND AWARDS

MAR 2021

Best graduating student civil engineering department 2019/2020 academic session – Akanuibiam Federal Polytechnic Unwana Having graduated as the best graduating student in civil engineering department 2019/2020 academic session with CGPA of 3.74/4.00

RECOMMENDATIONS

Emerike Obumneme Abraham – Colleague – Emerkeobumneme@yaho o.com – (+234) 07033466660

Was course mate in civil engineering department from first year till graduation and my working colleague

FIRST REFEREE

OCT 2020 - CURRENT

Engr. Prof Lawrence. O. Ettu

Mobile: +234 803 677 3326

SECOND REFEREE

OCT 2020 - CURRENT

Engr. Mrs Amatobi

Mobile: +234 803 304 6265

VOLUNTEERING

APR 2011 - CURRENT

President catholic alter server's association of Nigeria (CASAN)

President catholic alter server's association of Nigeria ST Basil's catholic church Ndiechi igbeagu IZZI local government Area Ebonyi State